辛普森一家
第二十四季 第十二集
SPS辛普森一家字幕组倾情呈现
字幕仅供学习交流之用 本片版权归FOX所有
春田同位素队 春季练习赛门票开售 看我蓄势待发
我没有获得"最佳脏话奖"提名
翻译: 旗木 井脑湿
后期: 旗木 盖罗  监制: MarcoII
♪ Szyslak一家 ♪
♪ The Szyslaks. ♪
早就被砍了
Already cancelled.
欢迎加入 SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 参与翻译后期
详情搜索 Google 或 新浪微博
我对女人的全部认识
Everything I know about women
可以用一首跳绳谣来总结
can be summed up by a jump-rope rhyme:
女孩前往火星 去买糖棒棒
"Girls go to Mars to buy candy bars,
男孩前往木星 变成笨蛋蛋
boys go to Jupiter to get more stupider."
不过我用不着前往木星去变笨蛋
Except I didn't have to go to Jupiter to get stupider.
我身边有个更大号球体可以观察
I had a bigger ball of gas I could study.
前方0.3米处请右转弯
In three-tenths of a mile, make a right turn.
Homer 听着GPS开车啊
Homer, listen to the GPS.
- 右转 - Homer 看路啊
- Turn right - Homer, watch the road!
- 上第一大道 东行 - 不是这条道 另一条
- onto First Street, head east. - Not this road, the other road!
俩姐姐 拜托
Ladies, please!
你们可以指使我 但别一块上啊
You can boss me around, just one at a time!
- 行至主街 - 周日之行都让你毁了
- On Main Street... - Our Sunday drive is ruined!
常春台
导航     菜单      进入
- 现在请右转 - 手握于十点和两点方向
- turn right now. - Hands at ten and two!
你有没有听啊? 人家说左转 不是右转
What are you doing? It said turn left, not right.
动画物理指标
搞毛啊?
What the...?
下面转为男声...
Switching to male voice...
...好让你听话
...so you will obey.
可算来了个管事的
Finally! A supervisor!
所以我身边最接近男性榜样的人
So the closest thing I had to an adult male role model
只剩下校霸了
were the schoolyard bullies.
嘿 Simpson
Hey, Simpson!
我命你把这只毛毛虫放到那女孩裙子里
I dare you to stick this caterpillar down that girl's dress.
不能把它放进Skinner的汉堡里吗?
Can't I just stick it in Skinner's sloppy joe?
那它就变成我汉堡里唯一的肉材了
It would actually be the only meat in said Joe.
不是什么事都能靠涮Skinner解决 Bart
Not everything can be solved with Skinner pranks, Bart.
没错 从Skinner思维里滚出来
Yeah, think outside the Skinner box.
嘿 看啊
Hey, look,
我们参演的电影入围奥斯卡了
that movie we were in got short-listed for an Oscar.
校霸
叼爆了
Awesome!
谁把这毛茸茸的家伙塞到我后背的?
Who's that stickin' a fuzzy-wuzzy down my back?
Mary Spuckler
Mary Spuckler!
♪ Kenny Rogers - Lady
♪ 女孩 ♪
♪ Lady ♪
♪ 我是你身披光辉盔甲的骑士 ♪
♪ I'm your knight in shining armor ♪
♪ 我爱你 ♪
♪ And I love you. ♪
我以为你离家出走去做明星了
I thought you left home to be a star.
嗓音好又有梦想的13岁女孩太多了
There's a lot of 13-year-olds out there with a voice and a dream.
我只找到个手模的活
I only got work as a hand model.
让他知道你没虱子
香奈儿5号更古
青少年香水
那是你的手?
That's your hand?
只有拇指是 你想我吗?
Just the thumb. Did you miss me?
快别碍我眼了 臭丫头
Get out of my face, cootie breath!
我真的想你
I did miss you.
你臭死了
You stink!
周六来找我
Come over Saturday.
现在我得把你推进泥塘了
I'm gonna have to push you in the mud now.
你敢推倒我试试 小子
Don't you pig-waller me, mister!
尽管来吧 亲爱的
Do what you must, darlin'.
这下可算补偿我昨天被老爸揍的那顿了
That sure makes up for my dad beating me last night.
还有我的阅读障碍
And for my dyslexia.
Mary?
谢天谢地今天穿的内裤只是边上破洞
Thank God I wore the underwear with the hole on the side.
现在才早上八点啊
It's 8:00 in the morning.
我可是农场女
I'm a farm girl.
已经给牛挤了奶
I already milked the cows,
控制了一场草场混乱
overcame a bout of prairie madness,
还给你做了点香肠和饼干
and made you some sausage and biscuits.
下雨真的好浪漫 你不觉得吗?
Rain is so romantic, don't you think?
你也看到了
You get the picture.
完美女神
Perfect girl.
我傻乎乎的像对待隔夜的无酵饼一样招待了她
So like a schmuck, I treat her like day-old matzo.
瘟疫站3
生物危害 生物危害 生物危害
无国界医生 你们就要变成无脸颊医生了
Doctors Without Borders, you're now doctors without faces!
Bart 什么时候做点女生感兴趣的事
Bart, when are we gonna do girl things,
比如抓青蛙或者打腿架
like catch a frog or leg wrestle?
马上 宝贝 马上
Soon, baby, soon.
等我杀掉Milhouse的傀儡
Let me just kill Milhouse's character.
他还以为我们是一伙呢
He thinks we're on the same team.
你又背叛我
Betrayed again!
Mary 我能跟Bart说句话吗?
Mary, could I steal Bart for a minute?
问他女朋友 问游戏
Ask his girlfriend, the game.
Mary 你知道你是我约过最酷的人啊
Oh, Mary, you know you're the coolest person I've ever hung out with.
又背叛我
Another betrayal!
Bart Simpson
Bart Simpson,
我不知道你的未来会是什么样
I don't know what the future holds for you...
够幸运就是我 再不济就是他
If you're lucky, me, then this.
但Bart 有件事我很清楚
...but, Bart, I do know this:
你不会比Mary Spuckler更出色
you will not do better than Mary Spuckler,
所以别为了什么破游戏就扔下她
so don't ignore her for a stupid video game!
嘿 放轻松
Hey, relax.
她知道她是我眼角边上的苹果
She knows she's the apple of the corner of my eye.
Bart 介意我跟我妈通个话吗?
Bart, do you mind if I call my mother?
随便
Not at all.
妈妈 过来接我 我腻死了
Mama! Come pick me up, I'm bored!
你等会儿的啊
You'll have to wait!
咱家驴打瞌睡呢
The mule's takin' a nap!
但愿是在瞌睡
We hope it's a nap.
吃晚饭咯
Dinnertime!
今晚我们享用城里人为了脱身
Now, let's enjoy the granola bars that city fella
送给我们的燕麦棒
gave us in exchange for lettin' him go.
算给那城里人上了一课 让他记得传承我们的民歌
That'll teach him to try to preserve our folk singing for posterity.
让我爸早上三点从国家公共广播台听这个
Just wait till my dad hears this at 3:00 a.m. on NPR.
他就知道我没浪费生命了
It'll prove I'm not wasting my life.
知道你毁了这次录音吗?
You realize you just ruined the recording.
你们家真是音乐才子辈出
A lot of musical talent in this house.
不过谁也比不过你吹的叶笛
But no one blows on a blade of grass like you.
再有八次分期付款 它就属于我了
Eight more payments and I own this.
但你确定不会再去打你没够的游戏了吗?
But are you sure there ain't no video game you'd rather be playin'?
我的眼里只有你 宝贝
All eyes on you, baby.
那你睁大眼睛竖好耳朵 听好看好了
Well, tell your eye-ears to watch-listen to this!
♪ 我原以为 我爱流浪 ♪
♪ I used to think I wanted to roam ♪
♪ 天涯海角 却难寻得 ♪
♪ But there ain't not never no place ♪
♪ 佳境如家 ♪
♪ None better than home ♪
数数有几个否定词 你就明白啦
Count the negatives, it all works out.
♪ 人们常说心在哪里家就在哪 ♪
♪ They say that home is where the heart is ♪
♪ 我却要说Bart在哪家就在哪 ♪
♪ But for me it's where the Bart is... ♪
你又在干嘛?
Now what are you doing?
我整首歌都为你而写 Bart Simpson
I wrote a whole song for you, Bart Simpson.
只求你认认真真听完
Least you could do is pay me full mind.
我要拿它去参加比赛
I was gonna enter it in a competition.
乡巴佬达人赛 头等奖: 诈骗唱片公司合约
那你赢定了
Well, you're gonna win,
因为你就是明星的料
'cause you've got star quality.
就像客串别人电影的绿巨人一样
Like the Hulk in movies other than The Hulk.
你知道吗?
You know what?
你总是时不时妙语连珠
Every now and then you say the perfect thing.
Mary 轮到我们用男朋友房间了
Mary, it's our turn to use the boyfriend room.
你俩根本没有男朋友
Y'all don't have boyfriends.
我们要和这个法加混血山地人练习吻功
We's gonna practice kissing with this French-Canadian mountain man.
你们为什么把我带到这儿? (法语)
Pourquoi m'avez-vous amené ici?
他还戴着脚镣呢
He's still wearing leg shackles.
人无完人嘛
All men is unpolished stones.
你们答应给我的威士忌呢? (法语)
Ou est le whisky que vous m'avez promis?
后来我就跑回家见你了
And then I ran right home to you.
你干得太漂亮了 Bart
You did everything great, Bart.
还把这一切都告诉了我 真是纯爷们
Then you told me all about it like a true gentleman.
我等不及要拿这套哄哄Lisa
I can't wait to use your moves on Lisa.
恶心
Ew!
360度无死角 恶心
On every level, ew!
Bart 你应该认认真真对待女孩子
Bart, you have to treat girls like they matter,
人家可不是一捆Milhice
not like they're a bunch of Milhice.
怎么了? Milhouse的复数形式 不信去查
What? It's the plural of Milhouse. Look it up.
持刊人之刊 iPad的威胁
听你妹妹的 小子
Listen to your sister, boy.
我说的话对你同样受用 老爸
What I'm saying applies to you, too, Dad.
瞎说什么呢?
What are you talkin' about?
Marge我俩处得可好了
Marge and I are goin' great.
Homer Simpson
Homer Simpson!
你是不是带Maggie去Moe那儿了?
Did you take Maggie to Moe's?
是趁"开心时刻"去的
It was during Happy Hour.
你不想咱家孩子开开心心吗?
Don't you want our baby to be happy?
看没看见?
Don't you see?
你根本没把女人当回事
You're taking women for granted.
抛除你这一概而论后总结一下
And aside from being lumped together and generalized about,
女人最讨厌就是这种事
it's the one thing all women hate.
我就不信受用Bart的东西还能受用我
How can something that applies to Bart apply to me?
我多成熟多睿智啊
I'm so much older and wiser.
我看是多秃顶多肥猪吧
More like balder and wider.
你这个小...
Why you little...
我让你跟我玩音近词的鬼把戏
I'll teach you to say something that sounds similar!
乡巴佬达人赛 春田剧院
感谢最后一位参赛者
Thank you, last contestant.
明天我们将锁定不再含有种族歧视的乡村喜剧
Tomorrow we will feature the no-longer racist country comedy
由卫星电视工作者Barry奉上
of Barry the Satellite TV Guy.
要说所有人都是平等的真是可笑
Isn't it funny how all people are of equal worth?
请不要抵制我的系列电动工具
Please do not boycott my line of power tools.
现在Barry的槽点都集中到她前妻身上了
Now all Barry's jokes are about his ex-wife.
胡说 我们已经复合了
No, they ain't. We're back together.
那你没什么戏头了
Then you got no act.
接下来 冠军就是...
And now, the winner is...
Devon Peacock
Devon Peacock!
这下有钱去修我的吊带扣了
I can finally get my suspender buckled!
看来我们跟Peacock一家又有仇了
Looks like we got a feud with the Peacocks now.
世仇录
海菲茨一家 (详参《血仇》)
奥地利哈布斯堡王室
时代华纳有线
该死的提线木偶
我的灰趾甲
Peacock一家
我只在乎你怎么想 Bart
All I care is what you think, Bart.
称赞她
Compliment her.
我哪知道她想听什么
I don't know what she wants.
看看我的英雄们怎么说
What would my heroes say?
扇她耳光 Bart
Slash her face now, Bart.
在她最不想被扇时扇她
Slash it while she least expects it.
Max Weinberg: 东大街乐队鼓手
Bart 告诉Mary玩鼓
Bart, tell Mary to play the drums...
甭管什么乐队 成员都得听鼓手的节奏
the only thing anyone listens to in any band.
要挑出一个点子也太难了
It's hard to pick just one of those.
Bart 你不妨多管齐下
Bart, you'd better get your act together.
就像我
And me, too.
我这会儿正要把衬衣送到干洗店
I've gotta get these shirts to the dry cleaners.
他们六点就关门了
They close at 6:00.
Bart Simpson 先从你的极度神游症里走出来
Bart Simpson, you get out of that gosh-darned fugue state this instant.
给我打打气
Lift my spirits!
那个... 给人打气可是个很有趣的话题
Um... lifting people's spirits is an interesting topic.
数世纪以来尼安德特人还有宇航员们
For centuries, Neanderthal and astronaut alike
都致力于给人打气
have enjoyed lifting spirits.
你怎么拿上课的腔调对付我
You're givin' me book report talk.
打扰了 我是一位巴西唱片制作人
Excuse me, I am a Brazilian record producer.
坛罐乐队: 以口琴等为乐器 以敲打坛罐等加强节奏效果的即席演奏乐队
我专注于迅速发展的坛罐乐队及桑巴舞蹈混合市场
I concentrate in the rapidly-growing jug band-samba fusion market.
天啊
Oh, my God!
您知道Billy-Bobaloo Skeeter-Rodriguez吗?
Do you know Billy-Bobaloo Skeeter-Rodriguez?
知道他?
Know him?
他成名前 还诱拐过我老妈呢
Before he was famous, he kidnapped my mother!
Mary 你愿意和我还有我万人迷的帅气儿子共进晚餐吗?
Mary, would you like to have dinner with me
and my handsome, girl-crazy son tonight?
我是第一个拥有个人酒水广告的男孩
I am the first boy to get my own liquor ad.
全球最有故事的男孩
Bart 你要一起来吗?
Bart, you want to come with us?
我需要你
I need you.
Mary 我们刚才一起听了三小时音乐
Mary, we've just been through three hours of music.
一般我每周只听一小时的
Usually, I only have music one hour a week,
而且老师还会用那段时间读火焰岛的房产报告
and the teacher spends it reading real estate listings for Fire Island.
那以后见了 Bart
I'll see you later, Bart.
Mary 你还好吧?
Mary, are you okay?
当然
Sure.
一切都很好
Everything's fine.
在那一刻我就预见到 在我生命里
At that moment, I had a vision of every time in my life
女人一生气 肯定会说 一切都很好
an angry woman would say "Everything's fine."
欢迎回家 亲爱的
一切都很好
看来只剩下我跟狗了
I guess it's just me and the dog.
一切都很好
Everything's fine.
现在
Now.
我的成绩?爱情零分  这根本不是是锻炼  她为何离开我
Melvis?
你姐Mary呢?
Where's Mary?
我把你的忏悔转述给了我姐
I brung you regrets from my sister.
但她已经铁了心不为所动了
She has been de-avoidably untained.
我是被甩了吗?
Am I getting dumped?
恶搞美国电影导演伍迪·艾伦
听着 Bart 也许你因为没认真待Mary失恋了
Okay, Bart, maybe you blew it by taking Mary for granted.
女人是人生中最玄幻的谜团 就好像...
Woman are life's great mystery, along with
为什么去中餐馆他们要给我们盐和辣椒
why do they give you salt and pepper at a Chinese restaurant?
但如果你还有心一试
But if you want one more shot,
罗马神话中爱与美的女神
我知道一种约会能把铁心的阿弗洛狄忒
I know a date that will turn this mighty Aphrodite
变成你的"开罗紫玫瑰"
into your purple rose of Cairo.
那些都是我导的电影
Those are movies I made.
我毕生的精华
It's my oeuvre.
法语中oeuvre含"蛋"之意 作复数
听起来有点肮脏 但其实不是
It sounds dirty, but it's not.
春田电影院
游戏的规则
1939年法国导演让·雷诺阿作品
大家那么快就睡着了
Everyone's fast asleep.
真像我二婚的那天晚上
It's like my second wedding night,
当时走掉的人更多 而且还没有退款
except more walkouts and there were no refunds.
真是的...
Gee...
卿卿我我之所
明晚可以再见到你吗?
Can I see you tomorrow night?
当然 明天我跟另一个男朋友还会来这里
Sure, I'll be here with my other boyfriend.
他现在正看着我们呢
He's watching us now.
天啊
Oh, boy.
谈谈就好之处
好吧 Luann 事情这样就解决吧
Okay, Luann, it's all settled.
我们把Milhouse抛弃就好了
We're gonna ditch Milhouse.
Bart 我们最好还是分开吧
Bart, I think it's best if we take a break.
好主意 我可以朝着其他情侣扔鸡蛋啦
Good idea, I can chuck eggs at the other couples.
抱我 你个笨蛋
Just hug me, dummy.
拍背?
Back pats?
这是分手啊
This is a breakup.
你会好起来的
You'll be fine.
一个萝卜一个坑嘛
There's a pot for every possum.
再给我个机会
Give me another chance.
玩跷跷板的时候 我会更关照你的
I'll be way more attentive to your needs on the seesaw.
只要你乐意 我就一直在底下不起来
I'll stay down there for as long as you want.
对不起 Bart 我是个13岁的乡下姑娘
Sorry, Bart, I'm a hillbilly girl of 13.
如果接下来的几个月还不结婚
If I'm not married in the next few months,
就没有人会要我了
nobody's gonna want me.
甚至老邋遢Joe都不会要我
Not even old Joe Clabby.
嘿 你真是个漂亮的小尤物 真的
Hey, you're a pretty little thing, you are,
但时间不等人哟
but ticktock, ticktock.
再见了 Bart
Good-bye, Bart.
宝贝
Aw, sweetie.
我早告诉过你 不近亲结婚就会落得这种下场
I told you this would happen if you dated outside the family.
快走吧 你们的关系结束了
Move along, relationship's over.
赶别人离开场地什么的 最喜欢了
Sure do like forcing people to leave areas.
在Patty新女性朋友的流动报刊亭试营业大典上
I was the only without a date at Patty's new lady friend's
我是唯一一个没有男伴的
travel bookstore soft opening.
是你说的 去不去由我的嘛
You told me it was up to me if I wanted to go.
你应该知道 我说我不在乎
You should know that me saying I don't care
意思就是我最在乎不过了
means I couldn't care more.
我最烦破译你这些东西
I am sick and tired of trying to decode you
就像你跟我是完全不同的一个人种似的
like you're some kind of human being separate from myself.
Bart 你回房间去好吗?
Bart, would you go to your room
你爸爸和我在谈点小事情
while your father and I finish our little talk?
小事情?
Little talk?
你们是在大吵架吧
You guys are having a big fight.
女人都有这个德性
This is the problem with women--
在无可挽回之前决不清楚告诉你她们要什么
they don't say what they mean until it's too late.
行 好吧
All right, fine.
你们男人要听 我就告诉你们我心里怎么想
If you boys want it, I'll tell you what I really think.
终于啊 有点进展啦
Finally, we're getting somewhere.
你俩都滚到狗窝睡去
You're both in the doghouse,
In the doghouse本意"睡狗窝" 引申意为"赶出家门"
这说法有点误导 因为你们还不如狗呢
which is misleading 'cause I still like the dog.
把我的提箱给我 孩子
Hand me my suitcase, boy.
我什么时候才能有Krusty手提箱?
When do I get a Krusty suitcase?
等你长大了
When you're older.
破落者之家
如果你没有真正的家 现在算有了
老妈赶你出门的时候 你就来这儿?
So this is where you go when Mom kicks you out?
你说得好像这事儿常有一样
You're saying it like it happens all the time.
顺带说一声啊 我停车位上的油漆有点掉色啊
And by the way, the paint's a little faded on my parking spot.
这种也算白金会员的待遇?
You call this a platinum club experience?
我们马上去解决 Simpson先生
We'll get right on it, Mr. Simpson.
我都说了一千遍了 叫我Homer就好
I told you a thousand times, call me Homer.
墙上贴的这须知是什么?
Oh, what's this notice on the wall?
酒店那套陈词滥调呗
Standard hotel boilerplate.
"本房间在过去的72小时内死过人"什么的
It just says somebody died in this room in the last 72 hours.
靠 我们居然错过了
Aw, man, we just missed it.
还会有人死在这的 儿子
Oh, it'll happen again, son.
我要去打个电话
Um, I've got to make a phone call.
随便你啦
Eh, knock yourself out.
警戒线 请勿穿越
又这样
Not again.
Mary? 真奇怪啊
Mary? Ooh, that's odd.
我还以为我打的是"不要自杀热线"呢
I thought I was calling the Suicide Not Line,
因为我过得很好啊
because I'm doing great.
那 你在分开的时间里过得如何?
So, um, how are you handling taking a break?
挺好 原来Adele是对的
Great. Turns out Adele was right.
大脑被爱情这颗钉子猛扎一下
Ain't nothing better for songwriting
再没什么比写歌更治愈了
than when your relationship takes a bolt to the brain.
听听你的评价啊
Tell me what you think.
♪ 我跟男人分了手 ♪
♪ I broke up with a fella ♪
♪ 但我并不哀愁 ♪
♪ But I ain't grieving ♪
♪ 他没啥水平 ♪
♪ He was much too proud ♪
♪ 却还骄傲得不行 ♪
♪ Of underachieving ♪
防冻剂
耗子药
♪ 不敢相信我喜欢过他 ♪
♪ I can't believe I liked him ♪
♪ 当时真是睁眼瞎 ♪
♪ I must have been blind ♪
♪ 他不是那么聪明帅气 ♪
♪ He wasn't so smart or handsome ♪
♪ 或者体贴用心 ♪
♪ Or kind ♪
♪ 跟他在一起的每分每秒 ♪
♪ Every moment with that boy ♪
♪ 实在糟糕透顶 ♪
♪ Was totally horrid ♪
♪ 他头发和前额的界线 实在不太分明 ♪
♪ And I can't even tell where his hair meets his forehead ♪
晚10点后禁止啜泣
我干嘛要给她买那本韵脚字典
Why did I buy her that rhyming dictionary?
韵脚词典
辞典作者名June Moon亦押韵
♪ 现在我睁开了双眼 ♪
♪ My eyes are wide open ♪
♪ 看清了他的缺点 ♪
♪ Now I see his warts ♪
♪ 希望他万事如意 虽然他身在地狱 ♪
♪ I wish him well, down in hell ♪
♪ 在那里 他只有吃自己的短裤 ♪
♪ Where he'll eat his own shorts. ♪
我不吐不快啊 就像毒蛇喷毒一样
It just poured out of me like venom from a snake.
我多年前就想这样干了 但你妈妈就是不准
I had this idea years ago, but your mother wouldn't let me do it.
这回证明她是多么...
shows how much she...
刺到我眼睛啦
It's hurting my eyes!
这里真是棒 没有老婆对你发飙
It's so great here-- no wife to get mad at you
就因为她们进来时候你立马关上电脑
for closing your laptop whenever they walk into the room.
要不就是让孩子染上大麻
Or getting your kid hooked on pot.
她也是我养大的孩子 知道不
She's my kid, too, you know.
知道我们需要啥不?
You know what we need?
经典的"扫地出门"大聚会
A classic "kicked out of the house" party.
谁有带劲的CD?
Now, who's got a rocking CD?
我这里有有Robert Caro的《权力之道》的音频书
I've got the audio book of Robert Caro's The Passage of Power.
权力之道: 美国第36任总统林登传记
就这玩意?
That's it?
行吧 给点力也行
Well, then let's "power" this party up.
总统御用专机 空军一号
Air Force One, the president's plane,
从驾驶舱后面被分为三个隔间
is divided behind the crew's cockpit into three compartments.
第一个隔间 就在驾驶舱后面
In the first of them, just behind the cockpit,
女人们坐着哭泣 特工们则努力不让眼泪流下
women sat weeping and Secret Service agents were trying to hold back tears.
"你听说过坚强的男人也会哭吗?
"You've heard of strong men crying?
我们那天就见到过" 一位记者回忆道
Well, we had it there that day," recalls a reporter.
飞行员驾驶着这架大飞机 从达拉斯跑道上飞起
As the pilot lifted the big jet off the Dallas runway,
爬升如此之陡峻 就像一个男人...
in a climb so steep that to a man...
我想Mary了
I miss Mary.
我想Roxie了
I miss Roxie.
我跟我孩子一起抽大麻的俱乐部就叫这个名字
That's the club where I used to smoke pot with my kid.
当机立断的时候到了
This calls for decisive action.
就像林登总统在哀悼期之后
Like LBJ's use of the period of mourning following
采取暗杀行动来推行民权法案
the assassination to push through the Civil Rights Act.
但我们怎么知道该做什么呢?
But how do we figure out what to do?
跟着好莱坞学嘛
The same way Hollywood does.
看点英国电影
By watching British movies.
爱 无疑
首相大人
The Prime Minister,
也就是说 我要做出一个爱的紧急宣言
that is to say, I would like to make an emergency declaration
对我那没钱却大方的秘书
of love to my poor but cheeky secretary.
什么? 我吗? 扁屁股Eliza?
What, me? Eliza Commonbottom?
我... 也就是说...
I... that is to say...
多说无益了
Flibberty-gibberty.
♪ 所有年轻的兄弟们呐 ♪ 嘿 兄弟们
♪ All the young dudes ♪ Hey, dudes
♪ 美闻传开呐 ♪
♪ Carry the news ♪
♪ 跳波加洛舞的兄弟们呐... ♪
♪ Boogaloo dudes... ♪
爱情比我所有的魔法都要强大
Love is more powerful than all my magic.
真难相信那个破国家以前是万国主宰
Hard to believe that country used to rule anything.
我同意 但是要赢回我们的女人
Agreed, but to win back our women,
我们需要一个宏大的浪漫场面
we need to make a grand romantic gesture.
我们同意
Hear, hear.
把电影看完再说
After we finish watching the movie.
♪ 美闻传开呐 ♪
♪ Carry the news ♪
♪ 年轻弟兄呐 ♪
♪ All the young dudes ♪
♪ 美闻传开呐 ♪
♪ Carry the news
♪ 听听这美闻 来吧 ♪
♪ Let's hear the news, come on. ♪
写得龙飞凤舞的
Hmm, cursive.
您被邀请参加一个大场面?
"You are invited to a grand gesture"?
♪ 写这首歌 是为说声对不起 ♪
♪ I wrote this song to say I'm sorry ♪
♪ 老爸 别把功劳都归自己 ♪
♪ Dad, don't be a credit hog ♪
♪ 曲子是贝多芬所作 ♪
♪ The melody is by Beethoven ♪
♪ 拍电影的写曲还真不错 ♪
♪ Not bad for a movie dog ♪
♪ 我不会再刨垃圾找吃的 ♪
♪ I'll stop eating from the garbage ♪
♪ Marge 最后一块猪排留给你 ♪
♪ Marge, you will get the last pork chop ♪
一张完成了的家务清单
A completed chore list.
我承诺在一年内把打了勾的全部办妥
And I promise to do the things I checked off within a year.
♪ 雀斑脸Mary 请原谅我 ♪
♪ Spuckler Mary, please forgive me ♪
♪ 再给我个机会重新来过 ♪
♪ All I ask is one more chance. ♪
Bart 你人是不错
Bart, you're a good duck,
但我们不会走太远
but we wouldn't last.
但这集我是主角啊
But I'm the main guy in this story.
我最后不应该是欢喜大结局吗?
Things are supposed to work out for me.
每个人都是自己故事里的主角
Everyone is the main guy in their own story.
朋友 欢迎来到我的故事里
My friend, welcome to my story.
那个时候我明白了
And that's when I learned
丘比特不过是个背着箭囊的死裸胖子
Cupid was just a fat, naked jerk with an arrow.
只是一次挫折 你不会就心灰意冷了吧?
But surely you didn't give up on love after just one setback?
爱情是我们唯一的抵御 对抗这毫无意义的宇宙深渊
Love is our only defense against the abyss in this meaningless universe.
爱情 是个什么东西?
Love-- what is it?
它有什么意义? 你怎么拼写它?
What does it mean? How do you spell it?
没人知道
No one knows.
幸好 治疗爱情有良方
Fortunately there is a cure.
世上任意一款电子游戏都行
Any video game ever made.
请记住 本游戏适用于14岁或以下儿童
Remember, this game is for age 14 or under.
火星武术大乱斗
如果您大于该年龄 请寻求救助
If you are older than that, please get help.
寻求救助 寻求救助
Get help, get help.
已婚?
Married?
婚恋状态: 已婚
婚恋状态: 单身
我想你
发送
一条信息 收取自...
One message received from...
小寡妇 Mary Spuckler
The widow Mary Spuckler.
干得好 Bart
Well done, Bart.
你表现得就像
You played that like a combination
Willie Mays和Paul Cezanne的混合体一样
of Willie Mays and Paul Cézanne.
前者为职棒运动员 后者为法国后印象派画家
你谁啊?
Who are you?
我... 你知道的 我扮演过《蚁哥正传》的蚂蚁
I... you know, I-I played the ant in Antz
蚂蚁电影里最不知名的那部...
the lesser known of the ant movies.
了解了
Oh, yeah.
欢迎加入 SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 参与翻译后期
详情搜索 Google 或 新浪微博